Contact

<u>Call & WhatsApp</u>: +92 346 530 5266 0334 566 8 445

<u>Email</u>: imran.lashari456@gmail.com <u>LinkedIn</u>:

www.linkedin.com/in/imran-lashari-91b703172

<u>GitHub</u>: https://github.com/imranlashari

Soft Skills

Project Management
Problem Solving
Client Dealing
Deliver on time
Team Lead

Development Skills

8 / 10
8 / 10
8 / 10
8 / 10
8 / 10
8 / 10
8 / 10
8 / 10
8 / 10
7/10
7/10
7/10
5/10
2/ 10

Certifications

1. Front-End Web Development EVS Institute, Rawalpindi, PK. (June-2019 to Sept-2019)

2. PHP Laravel Development EVS Institute, Rawalpindi, PK. (June-2019 to Sept-2019)

Imran Lashari

Full Stack Developer (Laravel | Vue.js | APIs | Payments gateways | Accounting System)



About

I am a motivated Full Stack Developer with 4+ years of working experience with different companies and projects. I want to join team of professionals to improve my skills as well as knowledge. I am passionate about technology, constantly seeking to learn and improve skillsets.

Working Experience with Tech & Stack

Stack			
HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, JQuery, Ajax, Laravel, MySQL			
Laravel & Vue.js (basic), Tailwind CSS, MySQL			

	Front-End Tech:		Back-End Tech:
•	HTML	•	Hands on Coding with PHP Laravel (5,6,7,8,9),
•	CSS		working on REST APIs
•	JAVASCRIPT	•	Experience with Deploying projects on AWS.
•	Bootstrap	•	Integrating external APIs in the Laravel projects
•	Javascript		like Stripe Payment & PayPal APIs
•	JQuery	•	Experience with queuing system such as
•	Figma to Responsive Web Pages		Queue Jobs and Cron Jobs
•	Ajax	•	Experience with Databases such as MySQL
•	Vue.Js (basic)	•	Knowledge of CI/CD pipelines
•	Vuex (basic)	•	Write code which optimizes api-calls and DB
•	Responsive Designs		load for the amazing mobile apps
•	PSDs to Responsive Web Pages		
		1	

Experience

Freelancer at UPWORK

Full Stack Laravel Developer (part time/ full time)

Responsibilities:

- Working on Laravel projects Project
- Creating and supporting all APIs and services that power our mobile App.
- APIs Development and Integration using Sanctum Authentication
- Maintaining Admin Panel & Dashboard
- Testing APIs using postman
- GitHub

KHARIDAAR, Lahore, Pakistan

Backend Laravel 8 API Developer (Part Time)
September-2021 to present

Responsibilities:

- Working on Pakistan's Largest B2B wholesale Project
- Creating and supporting all APIs and services that power our mobile App.
- APIs Development and Integration using Sanctum Authentication
- Maintaining Admin Panel & Dashboard
- Providing APIs to Mobile App Developer
- Accounting system (Assets, Payable, Receivables, Expenses, Ledger)
- Testing APIs using postman
- GitHub

PHPTRAVELS, Lahore, Pakistan

Backend Laravel 8 Developer

Total experience = 1 year

September-2021 to Auguest-2022

Responsibilities:

- Working on Pakistan's First Driverless Khudcar (Rent a Car) Project
- Creating and supporting all APIs and services that power our mobile App.
- APIs Development and Integration using Sanctum Authentication
- Maintaining Admin Panel & Dashboard
- Providing APIs to Mobile App Developer
- Testing APIs using postman
- GitHub

Chakor Software, Lahore, Pakistan

Full Stack (Laravel 8 + Vue.js) Developer Total experience = 4 months (Contractal) April-2021 to July-2021

Responsibilities:

- Dealing with a Canadian client
- Creating & maintaining complete web applications using Laravel
- Payment API Integrations (Stripe, PayPal, Flutter wave)
- Socialite API Integrations (Google, Facebook)
- Google Map API integration

Eden Spell Technologies, Rawalpindi, Pakistan

Laravel Developer

Total experience = 2 years 3 months (Full Time)

Octuber-2018 to January-2021

Responsibilities:

- Dealing with USA clients
- Managing the team
- Creating & maintaining complete web applications using Laravel
- Payment API Integrations (Stripe, PayPal, Flutter wave)
- Socialite API Integrations (Google, Facebook)
- Google Map API integration

PTCL Data Center, H-9, Islamabad, Pakistan

Linux System Administrator

June 2019 - August 2019 (3 months - Internship)

Education

Quaid-I-Azam University, Islamabad, Pakistan

4-years Bachelors of Computer Sciences (2014 - 2018) CGPA: 3.10 / 4.00

Islamabad Model College for Boys G-10/4, Islamabad, Pakistan

Primary, Elementary, SSC, HSSC, Pre-Engineering (2002 - 2014)